[
  {
    "Option-b:": "means inspections are not required.",
    "Option-a:": "makes test preparation easier.",
    "Answer: ": "c",
    "Question": "Q1:The most important thing about early test design is that it?",
    "Option-d:": "will find all faults.",
    "Option-c:": "can prevent fault multiplication."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "departure from specified behavior.",
    "Option-a:": "found in the software; the result of an error.",
    "Answer: ": "b",
    "Question": "Q2:A failure is?",
    "Option-d:": "a human action that produces an incorrect result.",
    "Option-c:": "an incorrect step, process or data definition in a computer program."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "test planning..",
    "Option-a:": "test recording..",
    "Answer: ": "c",
    "Question": "Q3:Test cases are designed during?",
    "Option-d:": "test configuration.",
    "Option-c:": "test specification."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "the analysis of batch programs.",
    "Option-a:": "the reviewing of test plansr.",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question": "Q4:Static analysis is best described as?",
    "Option-d:": "the analysis of program code.",
    "Option-c:": "the use of black box testing."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "the first testing that is performed.",
    "Option-a:": "post-release testing by end user representatives at the developer’s site.",
    "Answer: ": "c",
    "Question": "Q5:Alpha testing is?",
    "Option-d:": "pre-release testing by end user representatives at their sites.",
    "Option-c:": "pre-release testing by end user representatives at the developer’s site."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "An inspection has a trained leader, whilst a walkthrough has no leader.",
    "Option-a:": "An inspection is lead by the author, whilst a walkthrough is lead by a trained moderator.",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question": "Q6:What is the main difference between a walkthrough and an inspection?",
    "Option-d:": "A walkthrough is lead by the author, whilst an inspection is lead by a trained moderator.",
    "Option-c:": "Authors are not present during inspections, whilst they are during walkthroughs."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "Path testing.",
    "Option-a:": "Statement testing",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question": "Q7:Which of the following is NOT a white box technique?",
    "Option-d:": "State transition testing",
    "Option-c:": "Data flow testing"
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "Usability testing",
    "Option-a:": "Boundary value analysis",
    "Answer: ": "a",
    "Question": "Q8:Which of the following is a form of functional testing?",
    "Option-d:": "Security testing.",
    "Option-c:": "Performance testing."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "It only models the testing phase.",
    "Option-a:": "It states that modules are tested against user requirements.",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question": "Q9:Which of the following is true of the V-model?",
    "Option-d:": "It includes the verification of designs.",
    "Option-c:": "It specifies the test techniques to be used."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "equivalence partitioning.",
    "Option-a:": "syntax testing.",
    "Answer: ": "c",
    "Question": "Q10:Which of the following is not described in a unit test standard?",
    "Option-d:": "modified condition/decision coverage.",
    "Option-c:": "stress testing."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "the required level of confidence has been achieved.",
    "Option-a:": "time runs out.",
    "Answer: ": "b",
    "Question": "Q11:Enough testing has been performed when?",
    "Option-d:": "the users won’t find any serious faults.",
    "Option-c:": "no more faults are found."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "can only be used in component, integration and system testing.",
    "Option-a:": "supplements formal test design techniques.",
    "Answer: ": "a",
    "Question": "Q12:Error guessing?",
    "Option-d:": "is not repeatable and should not be used.",
    "Option-c:": "is only performed in user acceptance testing."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "Integration testing.",
    "Option-a:": "Regression testing.",
    "Answer: ": "a",
    "Question": "Q13:Which of the following is likely to benefit most from the use of test tools providing test capture and replay facilities?",
    "Option-d:": "ser acceptance testing.",
    "Option-c:": "System testing."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "a fault.",
    "Option-a:": "an error.",
    "Answer: ": "c",
    "Question": "Q14:A deviation from the specified or expected behavior that is visible to end-users is called?",
    "Option-d:": "a defect.",
    "Option-c:": "a failure."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "status accounting of configuration items.",
    "Option-a:": "auditing conformance to ISO 9000.",
    "Answer: ": "a",
    "Question": "Q15:Which of the following is NOT part of configuration management?",
    "Option-d:": "controlled library access.",
    "Option-c:": "identification of test versions."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "when time has run out.",
    "Option-a:": "when all the planned tests have been run.",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question": "Q16:When should testing be stopped?",
    "Option-d:": "it depends on the risks for the system being tested",
    "Option-c:": "when all faults have been fixed correctly."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "documentation.",
    "Option-a:": "requirements.",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question":"Q17:Incidents would not be raised against?",
    "Option-d:": "improvements suggested by users.",
    "Option-c:": "test cases."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "inspection.",
    "Option-a:": "walkthrough.",
    "Answer: ": "b",
    "Question": "Q18:What type of review requires formal entry and exit criteria, including metrics?",
    "Option-d:": "post project review.",
    "Option-c:": "management review."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "as the first approach to deriving test cases.",
    "Option-a:": "after more formal techniques have been applied.",
    "Answer: ": "a",
    "Question": "Q19:Error guessing is best used?",
    "Option-d:": "after the system has gone live.",
    "Option-c:": "by inexperienced testers."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "unreachable (“dead”) code.",
    "Option-a:": "the use of a variable before it has been defined",
    "Answer: ": "c",
    "Question": "Q20:What can static analysis NOT find?",
    "Option-d:": "array bound violations.",
    "Option-c:": "memory leaks."
  },
  {
    "Option-b:": "Requirement Phase",
    "Option-a:": "Testing Phase",
    "Answer: ": "d",
    "Question": "Q21:Which of the following is not a valid phase of SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle)??",
    "Option-d:": "Testing closure",
    "Option-c:": "Deployment phase"
  }
]